module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'this nfl running back was on the US 1992 olympic bobsled team', 
      a: 'hershell walker', 
      b: 'marshall faulk',
      c: 'christian okoye',
      d: 'thurman thomas',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'baseball player mookie bets competed in the 2015 & 2017', 
      a: 'US open (golf)', 
      b: 'world series of bowling',
      c: 'professional darts championships',
      d: 'ironman lake placid',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'before being drafted to the MLB in 1978, he had signed a letter of intent to play QB at washington state', 
      a: 'cal ripken jr', 
      b: 'kirk gibson',
      c: 'ryan sandberg',
      d: 'tom brunansky',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'golfer john daly still holds multiple high school records for the sport of', 
      a: 'soccer', 
      b: 'wrestling',
      c: 'baseball',
      d: 'football',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'football legend jim brown was an second team all american in', 
      a: 'lacrosse', 
      b: 'track & field',
      c: 'baseball',
      d: 'basketball',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'this notre dame and NFL wide receiver was drafted by the MLB twice but stuck with the pig skin', 
      a: 'raghib ismail', 
      b: 'golden tate',
      c: 'michael floyd',
      d: 'jeff samardzija',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'this hall of fame pitcher was drafted into the NHL in 1984 ahead of brett hull', 
      a: 'orel hershiser', 
      b: 'bret saberhagen',
      c: 'tom glavine',
      d: 'roger clemens',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'before hitting 270 home runs as a cincinnati red, adum dunn was at the university of texas', 
      a: 'on the rowing team', 
      b: 'played forward in basketball',
      c: 'threw discus on track & field',
      d: 'played qb in football',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'before his nba hall of fame career, he set a state hs record with 7 interceptions in a single game', 
      a: 'allen iverson', 
      b: 'isiah thomas',
      c: 'steve nash',
      d: 'tony parker',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'in addition to football, pro bowler nate ebner also', 
      a: 'qualified for the 2017 us open of golf', 
      b: 'played rugby in the 2016 olympics',
      c: 'won american ninja warrior',
      d: 'boxed under a false identity',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};